[{
    "id":"1",
    "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
    "answer": "4",
    "questionDifficulty":{
        "SQL": 6,
        "Python": 6
    }
}
,

{
    "id":"2",
    "question": "What is 2 * 10?",
    "answer": "20",
    "question difficulty":{
        "SQL": 6,
        "Python": 6
    }
},

{
    "id":"3",
    "question": "What is 9 + 9?",
    "answer": "18",
    "question difficulty":{
        "SQL": 6,
        "Python": 6
    }
},

{
    "id":"4",
    "question": "What is 52 - 23?",
    "answer": "29",
    "question difficulty":{
        "SQL": 6,
        "Python": 6
    }
},

{
    "id":"5",
    "question": "What is 25 / 5?",
    "answer": "5",
    "question difficulty":{
        "SQL": 6,
        "Python": 6
    }
},

{
    "id":"6",
    "question": "What is 10 * 10?",
    "answer": "100"
},

{
    "id":"7",
    "question": "What is 8 + 42?",
    "answer": "50",
    "question difficulty":{
        "SQL": 6,
        "Python": 6
    }
},

{
    "id":"8",
    "question": "What is 9 * 4?",
    "answer": "36",
    "question difficulty":{
        "SQL": 6,
        "Python": 6
    }
},

{
    "id":"9",
    "question": "What is 42 / 7?",
    "answer": "6",
    "question difficulty":{
        "SQL": 6,
        "Python": 6
    }

},

{
    "id":"10",
    "question": "What is 18 - 12?",
    "answer": "6",
    "question difficulty":{
        "SQL": 6,
        "Python": 6
    }
}]